as a comic I perform in a lot of unusual
places the strangest was that last year
I got asked to perform in a prison I'm
well I the judge said it's community
service hours but still I like to think
I have a prison ministry so anybody here
been to prison I'm am all right
I can say whatever I want okay good so
I'm in the performing area and it's very
odd because there are a hundred 50
convicts and I'm guarded by one female
guard with no gun it's like the cast of
Scarface guarded by film Alou what was
odd and really strange and freaked me
out a little bit was when I was done the
prisoner didn't leave that's like
evidently they had no other pressing
engagements so I am surrounded by a sea
of neck tattoos in the most frightening
meet-and-greet ever and as one man came
up and said I've been there 18 years and
that is the best time I have had in
those 18 years and that was the warden
so
but that's what touched me oh that's a
lie I mean it wasn't inmate I just feel
bad Sansa they made them but see I'm a
comedian and I take the truth and I
twist it for your amusement
you understand that why can't my wife
that's my point
people always ask where comedians get
their material and I'd have to be honest
things happen to us that don't happen to
doctors and lawyers I'll give you an
example I was at a convention and I was
sleeping all right I was rooming with
another comedian he's a road warrior and
he's training himself he can't sleep
unless the TV is on and and the lights
are on and he also has a sleep apnea
machine which is great if you like
sleeping next to Darth Vader all right
I've got earplugs that helps but I like
to sleep in the dark it's work
so I put a pillow over my head but like
to breathe another quirk I I don't I
didn't bring a sleep mask I don't know
what to do so mine I think all right I
don't know what am I getting
I do have clean underwear okay you're
ahead of me okay so I get up and I put a
pair on like a mask and it's great it's
got two openings for my ears and the
convenient opening for my nose it's
perfect if you want to catch on but a
lot of you are already there are you
there okay so I'm lying back in bed and
I feel like a superhero right now I
really do I feel like a I'm
tighty-whitey man that's who I am and
I'm waiting for my sidekick boxer boy
and we'll go fight our nemesis granny
panties so I'm it's great it works I'm
just about to fall asleep and I think to
myself what if I die like this like how
would they explain this to my wife I was
like mrs. Li we found your husband in
the hotel room with another man with
underwear on his head so I get up and I
write a note and I put in the pill next
to me it says if found dead please
remove underwear
I'm about to doze off and I realize got
to write another note the top ones
[Music]
you cannot be too careful so I fall
asleep it's great I wake up the next
morning to the sound of laughter and the
other comedian is laughing and they ask
if I'm a dyslexic dresser and it turns
out he's taking pictures of me and yes
then these posted them on Facebook
snapchat Instagram Twitter which sounds
bad but I got an endorsement deal from
fruit of the Loom so it's great that's
right at this age I'm an underwear model
thank you very much
[Laughter]
hey did you know the dry bark comedy has
their own app download it right now and
watch my whole special